

CONTACT



053 642 9660



ree8.2053@gmail.com



Dharhan, Saudi Arabia

SKILLS

- · Data mining tools.
- · Microsoft offices.
- Design Infographics and Diagrams.
- iOS and Android.
- JavaScript, PHP, C++, HTML5, CSS3.
- Asp.net, .net core framework
- WordPress, Shopify, Magneto platforms.
- Digital Marketing.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Desktop and Mobile application for Al-Hussaini Charity
- Built a model for the Gulf Agency Company to find the qualified people for a position form a pile of CVs.

LANGUAGE

English •••••

Arabic • • • • • •

REHAM KAMAL ALDUHAILAN

INFORMATION SYSTEM ANALYSTS

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Information Technology analyst with 3+ year in Real-Time Data Processing Saudi Aramco rigs drilling and Wire-line data.

As an engineer my aim is to obtain long-term engineering position within diverse environments where my knowledge, skills and experience are aptly utilized and challenged to meet the needs of growing global-minded company.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Information Systems (CIS)

Imam Abdulrahman Bin Faisal University - Dammam

EXPERIENCES

Baker Hughes

Dhahran

2019

Real Time System Specialist

Jan, 2021 - Present

- Resolved escalated issues by serving as subject matter expert (SME) on wideranging issues.
- Prepared reports by collecting, analyzing and summarizing information.
- Developed and maintained strong client relationships to deliver exceptional customer service and problem resolution.
- Created support documentation that enabled user community to extend skills, leverage system features and find resolutions to questions without intervention from support team.
- Analyzed transactions to build logical business intelligence model for real-time reporting needs.
- Created successful test scripts to manage automated feature testing by using testing methodology's

Al-Rugaib Furniture Company

Al-Khobar

Business Analyst

Dec, 2019 - Jan, 2021

- Sales analysis weekly report.
- Determine the problems or how to improve the existing business processes.
- Identify all the steps for the implementation of new features.
- Design the new features to implement.
- Analyze the impact of implementing new features.
- Documenting all the processes

Petrolink - COOP Training

Dhahran

System Developer Trainee

May, 2018 - Jul, 2018

Real-Time system administration, WITSML Data Control , Client / Contractor Support, Raw data collection, Conversion to WITSML, Delivery to WITSML databases.